{
    "subject": "Paul_Spence",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "FUBAR_2__film_",
    "human_readable": "Paul Spence created the film FUBAR 2.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9083268046379089,
            "question": "Who created the film FUBAR 2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.773793637752533,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Paul Spence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6796540021896362,
            "question": "Are there any other films created by Paul Spence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5799157619476318,
            "question": "Has Paul Spence won any awards for his work on FUBAR 2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4975314438343048,
            "question": "What is the plot of FUBAR 2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4708922207355499,
            "question": "When was FUBAR 2 released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45725956559181213,
            "question": "Is Paul Spence a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3870546817779541,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Paul Spence's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3712922930717468,
            "question": "Was FUBAR 2 a critical or commercial success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3475334346294403,
            "question": "What genre is FUBAR 2 likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Spence created the film FUBAR 2.",
            "html": "yago_10057_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was FUBAR 2 a critical or commercial success?",
            "html": "yago_10057_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes in Paul Spence's films?",
            "html": "yago_10057_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Paul Spence a filmmaker?",
            "html": "yago_10057_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10057_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10057_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10057_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10057_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10057_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10057_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10057_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10057_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10057_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10057_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports Paul Spence's involvement with the creation of \"FUBAR 2.\" Specifically, they mention that Paul Spence and David Lawrence are the actors playing Terry and Dean in the film series, and their experience and background directly influenced the making of FUBAR 2."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}